Guide to the National Campus Ministry Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
National Campus Ministry Association Records
1959-2014
RG 64
Yale University Divinity School Library
12.75
(32 boxes)
The main body of records dates from the N.C.M.A.'s planning stages in 1964 to 2006 and includes correspondence, minutes, reports, material pertaining to various committees, consultations, and conferences, related organizations, financial material, and printed material. The Association was formed to serve campus ministers by fostering their educational development, offering opportunities for support and communication, and providing channels for relating the resources of the university world to the shaping of the Church's policies and strategies for mission.
National Campus Ministry Association
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the N.C.M.A. and of John S. Duley
Biographical / Historical
The National Campus Ministry Association was founded in October 1964 at St. Louis, Missouri. Its first national conference was held in June 1965 at Michigan State University in East Lansing, Michigan. The N.C.M.A. was formed by a merger of the Association of Presbyterian University Pastors, the Campus Ministry Association, the Fellowship of Campus Ministry, and the National Association of College and University Ministers. Organizers of the N.C.M.A. recognized that campus ministers needed a clearer sense of support from their professional colleagues. The Association was formed to serve those in campus ministry by fostering their educational development, by offering opportunities for support, communication, celebration and personal growth, and by providing channels for relating the resources of the university world to the shaping of the Church's policies and strategies for mission.
At the time of the N.C.M.A.'s formation there was a close tie between the United Ministries in Higher Education and the new Association; most of the N.C.M.A.'s financial support came initially from the denominational boards involved in U.M.H.E. In 1967, the U.M.H.E.-related grants were combined into a contribution to the N.C.M.A. budget, and U.M.H.E. staff were "Loaned" to the N.C.M.A. to aid in the Association's development. Gradually, however, the N.C.M.A. felt that it needed to establish its own autonomy and direction. At a N.C.M.A.-U.M.H.E. Consultation held in February, 1972, it was decided that beginning in 1973, U.M.H.E. would no longer fund the N.C.M.A. as an organization, but would contribute financially to selected projects in the area of continuing education for ministers in higher education, an area of common concern. Since this decision, the N.C.M.A. budget has relied upon membership dues as its major source of income.
The National Campus Ministry Association has been the most inclusive and ecumenical of the professional campus ministry groupings. The Association has served as the bridge agency to the Lutheran Campus Ministry Association, the Catholic Campus Ministry Association, the Jewish Hillel Society, the United Ministries in Higher Education, and other similar groups. Many campus ministers are members both of the N.C.M.A. and a separate denominational campus ministry professional organization. The biennial conferences of the N.C.M.A. are held in cooperation with these other organizations. Through the N.C.M.A., the Women's Campus Ministry Caucus and the Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education Caucus were represented at the national level.
In its early years, the accent within the N.C.M.A. was on vocational status and academic responsibility, and the Association sent representatives to many of the academic professional societies. The emphasis then shifted to "advocacy", "action-research" projects, some of which failed for lack of interest. Historically, the strongest response has been to continuing education projects in the area of theology or family structure. The N.C.M.A. publishes a newsletter and sponsors conferences, seminars, and convocations. At present, its membership is primarily composed of personnel from the United Church of Christ, the United Presbyterian Church, the Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), the American Baptist Churches, the United Methodist Church, and the Reorganized Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints.
For more information, see the History of the NCMA booklet in Box 28, Folder 201.
Scope and Contents
The original collection, Series I, dates from the N.C.M.A.'s planning stages in 1964 to 1987 and includes correspondence, minutes, reports, material pertaining to various committees, consultations, and conferences, related organizations, financial material, and printed material. The material is divided according to academic years, beginning with 1964-65. The material dating from 1968-69 through 1972-73 was received in an organized state and the N.C.M.A. filing system has been kept intact, except in a few (noted) instances where labeled folders contained no material. The material prior to 1968-69 and after 1973 has been arranged to correspond with the N.C.M.A. filing system. The folder listing for the period 1968-73 reflects both the N.C.M.A. filing number system (in parentheses) and the Y.D.S.L. archival box and folder numbering system.
Series II and III represent additional materials received from the National Campus Ministry Association to document its ongoing activities. Series IV contains material from a participant in the NCMA, John S. Duley, who was a campus minister from 1948 to 1968.
The National Campus Ministry Association has served as an important channel of communication for campus ministers, providing supportive fellowship for individual members and a unified voice to the outside world. Consultations on complex, timely topics such as problem pregnancies, styles of ministry, and criminal justice have given members opportunities to exchange viewpoints, knowledge and expertise in dealing with a variety of problems. Some of the services the Association currently provides its members include a newsletter, sponsorship and co-sponsorship of regional and national conferences, information on job openings and continuing education opportunities, and other material about and for campus ministry.
The papers of the N.C.M.A. provide a valuable complement to other collections at the Yale Divinity Library that document religious work among college and university students, including the Archives of the New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education, the Archives of the Student Christian Movement in New England, the Archives of the Y.M.C.A.-Student Division, the Archives of the National Student Christian Federation, etc.
Arrangement
I. N.C.M.A. Filing System
II. 1997 Addendum
III. 2010 Addendum
IV. 2013 Addendum
V. 2015 Addendum
Universities and colleges -- Religion; Clergy; Coordinating Council of Professional Religious Associations in Higher Education; National Campus Ministry Association; National Institute for Campus Ministries; United Ministries in Higher Education
- N.C.M.A. Filing System, 1964-1987; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The material is arranged chronologically. Not all the contents are specifically listed.
  - 1964-1965
    - Minutes--Provisional Executive Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Minutes--Executive Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Constitution, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1965-1966
    - Minutes--Executive Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes--Project Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets re. study seminars and conferences, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1966-1967
    - Minutes--Executive Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Minutes--Administrative Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Minutes--Grants Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Minutes--Convocation Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Communications from the President, 1966-167 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Materials re. convocation held 1967 Jun 19-23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1967-1968
    - Minutes--Executive Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Minutes--Project Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Minutes--Southeastern "Regional" Conference Planning Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Communications from the President re. Constitutional revision, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Communications from the President re. NCMA elections, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Communications from the President re. Vietnam War, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Printed material related to seminars, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Committee on Action--Research regarding Criteria for Grants, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1967-1968
    - Budget and Finance (0.1.1), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - General (5.1), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Program and Conference (5.2), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of Meetings/Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5a)
    - Executive Committee (5.3), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - NCMA Applications (Lapsed or Withdrawn) - I, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - NCMA Applications (Lapsed or Withdrawn) - II, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Printed Material, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 8a)
    - Rosters, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 8a)
  - 1969-1970
    - Administration (0.1), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - General Matters (0.1.0), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Budget and Finance, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Checks and Bills (0.1.2), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Minutes of Meetings (0.1.3), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee (0.2), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Administrative Committee (0.2.1), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Women's Caucus (0.2.2), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Research and Grants (0.3), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Professional and Ecumenical Relations (0.3.1), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Continuing Education Seminars (0.3.2), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Continuing Education Seminars: The Leisure Revolution (0.3.2.1), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Continuing Education Seminars: Campus Ministry in Medical Education (0.3.2.2), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Continuing Education Seminars: Technology, Social Change and Education (0.3.2.3), 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Continuing Education Seminars: Problem Pregnancies (0.3.2.4), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Continuing Education Seminars: Insurance Forms (0.3.2.5), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Continuing Education Seminars: Continuing Education Insurance (0.3.2.6), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Annual Convocation (0.3.3), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Elections Committee (0.3.4), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Regional Representatives (0.4), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Regional Representatives: Region I (0.4.1), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Regional Representatives: Region II (0.4.2), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Regional Representatives: Region III (0.4.3), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Regional Representatives: Region IV (0.4.4), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Regional Representatives: Region V (0.4.5), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Regional Representatives: Region VI (0.4.6), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Regional Representatives: Region VII (0.4.7), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Regional Representatives: Region VIII (0.4.8), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Regional Representatives: Region IX (0.4.9), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Regional Representatives: Region X (0.4.10), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Regional Representatives: Region XI (0.4.11), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Regional Representatives: Region XII (0.4.12), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Application Process (0.5), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Renewals (0.5.1), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Mailing Lists (0.6.0), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Mailings to Exxecutive Committee (0.6.1), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence with President and Executive Committee (0.7.2), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - NCMA Constitution, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20a)
    - U.M.H.E., 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20a)
    - Pennsylvania Campus Ministry Association, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20a)
    - Catholic Campus Ministry Association, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20a)
    - Danforth Study Evaluations, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20a)
  - 1970-1971
    - Administration (0.1), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Administration:General Matters (0.1.0), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Administration:Budget and Finance (0.1.1), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Administration: Checks and Bills (0.1.2), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Adminstration: Minutes of Meetings (0.1.3), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Administration: Check Requisitions (0.1.4), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Administration: Central Service Orders (0.1.5), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Administration: Membership Income Statements (0.1.6), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Administration: Travel Expense Vouchers (0.1.7), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Administration: Multilith Order Forms (0.1.8), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee (0.2), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Executive committee: Administrative Committee (0.2.1), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Executive committee: Minutes (0.2.1.1), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Executive Committee: October 1970 Meeting (0.2.2) (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Executive Committee: Catholic Campus Ministry Association (0.2.3), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry Association (0.2.4), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Elections Committee (0.2.6), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Nominations Committee (0.2.6), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Executive Committee Minutes (0.2.7), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Consultations (0.3), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Consultations: Consultation on Styles of Theological Reflection (0.3.1), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Consultations: Prophetic Inquiry (0.3.2), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Consultations: Prophetic Inquiry, Pittsburgh (0.3.2a), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Consultations: Latin America (0.3.3), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Consultations: Styles of Ministry (0.3.4), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Consultations: Continuing Education Insurance (0.3.6), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Regional Representatives: Region I 0.4.1- Region III (0.4.3), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Regional Representatives: Region IV (0.4.4)- Region VII (0.4.7), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Regional Representatives: Region VIII (0.4.8)- Region XII (0.4.12), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Change of Address (0.5.2), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Mailings to Executive Committee (0.6.1), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (0.7); Requests for Information (0.7.0), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - President and Executive Committee (0.7.2), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Continuing Education (0.8), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Women's Caucus (0.8.1), 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - Black Caucus (0.8.2), 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 40A)
    - U.M.H.E., 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - National Division, Board of Global Ministries, United Methodist Church, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - University Common Ministry, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - National Association of College and University Chaplains, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - 1971-1972
    - Administration (0.1); General Matters (0.1.0); Budget and Finance (0.1.1), 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Checks and Bills (0.1.2), 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Minutes of Meetings (0.1.3), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Check Requisitions (0.1.4), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Central Service Orders (0.1.5), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Membership Income Statements (0.1.6), 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Travel Expense Vouchers (0.1.7), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Multilith Order Forms (0.1.8), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - N.C.M.A. Newsletters (0.1.9), 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Executive Committee (0.2), 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Administrative Committee (0.2.1), 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes (0.2.1.1), 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - October 1971 Meeting (0.2.2), 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Catholic Campus Ministry Association (0.2.3), 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry Association (0.2.4), 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Promotion (0.2.5), 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Election Committee (0.2.6), 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee Minutes (0.2.7), 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Communications Network (0.2.8), 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Consultations (0.3), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Insurance for Seminars (0.3.1), 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - Community College, St. Louis (0.3.2), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - American Family (0.3.3), 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - Prophetic Inquiry, Denver (0.3.5), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Alternate Styles of Education (0.3.6), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Criminal Justice, New York (0.3.7), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas (0.3.8), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - N.C.M.A.-U.M.H.E. Consultation, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Regional Representatives (0.4), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Charles Doak, Region I (0.4.1), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.1.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Robert Geller, Region II (0.4.2), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.2.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Paul Bodine, Region III (0.4.3), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.3.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - James Monroe, Region IV (0.4.4), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.4.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Peter Moe, Region V (0.4.5), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.5.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - William Webster, Region VI (0.4.6), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.6.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Norman Snook, Region VII (0.4.7), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.7.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Robert Thomason, Region VIII (0.4.8), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.8.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Lincoln Dring, Region IX (0.4.9 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.9.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Robert Boyer, Region X (0.4.10), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.10.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Frank Snow, Region XI (0.4.11), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.11.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Samuel Slie, Region XII (0.4.12), 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Rebates to Region (0.4.12.1 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Application Process (0.5 [Empty]), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - New Applicants (0.5.0), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
    - Renewals (0.5.1), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Change of Address (0.5.2), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Mailings - General (0.6), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Mailings to Executive Committee (0.6.1), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence (0.7), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Requests for Information (0.7.0), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - President and Executive Committee (0.7.1), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Continuing Education (0.8), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Women's Caucus (0.8.1), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Black Caucus (0.8.2), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - American Association for Higher Education, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 61A)
    - New Communities, Inc. (New York), 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - Peace Program, Northern California U.C.C. Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
    - United Campus Christian Ministry, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - 1972-1973
    - General Matters (0.1.0), 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Budget and Finance (0.1.1), 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Checks and Bills (0.1.2), 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Check Requisitions (0.1.4), 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Membership Income Statements (0.1.6), 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Travel Expense Vouchers (0.1.7), 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Multilith Order Forms (0.1.8), 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Mailing Lists (0.1.9), 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Executive Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 64A)
    - Administrative Committee (0.2.1), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - October 1972 Meeting Minutes (0.2.2), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Catholic Campus Ministry Association (0.2.3), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Lutheran Campus Ministry Association (0.2.4), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Promotion (0.2.5), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Election Committee (0.2.6), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Newsletter (0.2.7), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Communications Network (0.2.8), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Insurance for Seminars (0.3.1), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Community College, St. Louis (0.3.2), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Alternative Styles of Education (0.3.3), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Criminal Justice, New York (0.3.4), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - National Campus Ministers Conference (0.3.5), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Meditation Workshop (0.3.6), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Charles Doak, Region I (0.4.1), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Robert Geller, Region II (0.4.2), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Harold Wells, Region III (0.4.3), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - James Monroe, Region IV (0.4.4), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Donald Collins, Region V (0.4.5), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Richard Lundy, Region VI (0.4.6), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Norman Snook, Region VII (0.4.7), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Robert Thomason, Region VIII (0.4.8), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Loreda Jones, Region IX (0.4.9), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Robert Boyer, Region X (0.4.10), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Harold Smith, Region XI (0.4.11), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Samuel Slie, Region XII (0.4.12), 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - New Applicants (0.5.0), 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Renewals (0.5.1), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Change of Address (0.5.2), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Requests for Information (0.6.0), 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - President and Executive Committee Correspondence (0.6.1), 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - Women's Campus Ministry Caucus (0.7.1), 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - Black Campus Ministry Caucus (0.7.2), 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - Assn. of American Colleges Consultation - I, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Assn. of American Colleges Consultation - II, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - "Reports and Reflections" - N.C.M.A., 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Assn. for the Coordination of University Religious Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Ecology Task Force of the Southern California Council of Churches, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - Experimental Campus Ministry of St. Louis, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - U.M.H.E., 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - Ecological Concerns Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - International Intercollegiate Pentecostal Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - National Association of College and University Chaplains and Directors of Religious Life, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - U.S. Catholic Conference, Division of Higher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - 1973-1974
    - General Matters, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Executive Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Elections Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Regional Representatives, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - NCMA Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Budget and Finance (0.1.1), 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Check Requisitions (0.1.4), 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 83)